postchronicle.com 2018-02-03

# The Post Chronicle - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of the utmost importance to Post Chronicle. Our reputation and integrity is directly related to how we serve our clients and customers. Please find below a description of how Post Chronicle strives to protect the privacy of Internet users, and maintain the Internet as a highly credible medium. 

**User Information**

Post Chronicle does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private properties unless you specifically send us that information. If you fill out any form on the website or send an e-mail as a response to any article, your comments become public domain and we reserve the right to print or not print them. 

The Post Chronicle does, however, collect information which is specific to how you use the Internet. Post Chronicle servers note non-personally identifying details such as, but not limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of protecting those who utilize the Post Chronicle Network. 

**The Cookie Principle**

Post Chronicle may use cookies to improve your web browsing experience. When you first visit Post Chronicle, Post Chronicle may assign a unique random number to your computer browser - commonly known as a "cookie." We do this to understand the way a user responds to the services we deliver. For example, this number lets us keep track of how many times you visit...thus enhancing your online web viewing experience. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire.

DoubleClick DART cookie:

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Interest-Based Advertising

Interest-based advertising by Google will allow advertisers to show ads based on a user's previous interactions with them, such as visits to advertiser website and also to reach users based on their interests (e.g. "sports enthusiast"). To develop interest categories, Google will recognize the types of web pages users visit throughout the Google content network. As an example, if they visit a number of sports pages, we will add them to the "sports enthusiast" interest category. 

**For Web Publisher Members of Post Chronicle**

Post Chronicle regards all personal information collected from its web publisher members as completely confidential. This includes personal data provided during registration processes and financial account information. Post Chronicle does offer to advertisers any data which may facilitate the sale of advertising for a member site. This includes traffic data, click-thru rates, unique visitor information, web site geographic location, content information, and any demographic information offered by the web site member for the purpose of facilitating an advertising sale.

**Disclosure**

Post Chronicle openly volunteers its practices of collecting information, its targeting capabilities, and its use of cookies. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to webmaster@PostChronicle.com

Post Chronicle reserves the right to change our policy from time to time. A revised policy will apply to information collected after the date the policy is changed. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
